I etched the face of a stopwatch
Gravei a frente de um cronómetro
On the back of a raindrop
No verso de uma gota
And did a swap for the sand in an hourglass
E fiz a troca da areia numa ampulheta
I heard an unhappy ending
Ouvi um final infeliz
It sort of sounds like you leaving
Pareceu-me o som da tua despedida
I heard the piledriver waltz
Ouvi a valsa do bate-estacas
It woke me up this morning
Acordou-me esta manhã
You look like you've been for breakfast
Tens ar de quem foi tomar o pequeno-almoço
At the heartbreak hotel
Ao hotel do desgosto
And sat in the back booth by the
E se sentou na mesa de trás ao lado dos
Pamphlets and the literature on how to lose
Panfletos e da literatura sobre perder
Your waitress was miserable and so was your food
A empregada de mesa estava miserável e a comida também
If you're gonna try and walk on water
Se vais tentar caminhar sobre a água
Make sure you wear your comfortable shoes
Certifica-te que levas sapatos confortáveis
Mysteries flashing amber go green when you answer
O mistério da luz intermitente fica verde quando respondes
But the red on the rest of the questionnaire
Mas o vermelho no resto do questionário
Never changes
Nunca muda
I heard the news that you're planning
Ouvi dizer que fazes planos
To shoot me out of a cannon
Para me disparar de um canhão
I heard the piledriver waltz
Ouvi a valsa do bate-estacas
It woke me up this morning
Acordou-me esta manhã
You look like you've been for breakfast
Tens ar de quem foi tomar o pequeno-almoço
At the heartbreak hotel
Ao hotel do desgosto
And sat in the back booth by the
E se sentou na mesa de trás ao lado dos
Pamphlets and the literature on how to lose
Panfletos e da literatura sobre perder
Your waitress was miserable and so was your food
A empregada de mesa estava miserável e a comida também
If you're gonna try and walk on water
Se vais tentar caminhar sobre a água
Make sure you wear your comfortable shoes
Certifica-te que levas sapatos confortáveis
Piledriver
Bate-estacas